<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ian&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://ianbruyere.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ian&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 23:22:27 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ianbruyere.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Commit #2</title>
      <link>https://ianbruyere.github.io/posts/the-weekly-commit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 23:22:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ianbruyere.github.io/posts/the-weekly-commit-2/</guid>
      <description>Week 2 The Doing Not too much doing. The crush of Christmas and New Years being what it is. Mainly finding the threads of where I left off in my own code. Mainly in the testing section, simply need to remember where I was questing.
Learning Did some brief overview of security stuff. Mainly laying down some lead lines for future(far off) endeavors. Nothing much.
Near-Future Goals About the same. Start on my project in earnest as time and sanity allows, also keep up with my own small projects as buffers against code-block and staleness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Commit #1</title>
      <link>https://ianbruyere.github.io/posts/the-weekly-commit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 21:31:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ianbruyere.github.io/posts/the-weekly-commit-1/</guid>
      <description>Week 1 The Doing Made a CLI in python to process some Personal Training Data. It&amp;rsquo;s standard as dataprocessing goes: input a csv, clean it, outputs interesting information in csv. Other than being practically useful for myself, it allowed me to scrape the rust off my Python. The Python Standard Library is vast, and my goal of having it close at hand is only possible through constant practice. Suddenly having full-time work day disrupted my rhythm; doing some personal coding is a sign I haven&amp;rsquo;t lost the beat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
